It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on TV
But where are those
good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who
positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry
He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy!
I tell you, Sundays are
the best, aren't they?
You said it, chief.
Hey, Chris, what's the name of the girl
on the end of the couch?
I'm sure I've met her before.
I'll introduce myself to her.
That'll get her to say it.
Hi. I'm Chris.
Hi, Chris.
Well, that didn't work.
This Sunday
at the Quahog Convention Center,
it's Streaming-Con.
All your favorite YouTubers,
Instagrammers,
social media mavens and digital
influencers under one roof.
Social media? Better swap
my glasses for a monocle
that will pop out when
I'm confronted with modern talk.
LOL at thousands of the hottest
Vimeos, memes,
- epic fails.
- Heavens!
Meet disgraced YouTube star
Logan Paul and his cool bus,
the Golden Throated Homeless Guy
and his cool bus he poops in,
Newly Sober Cat...
formerly Grumpy Cat...
- and teen influencers Tyler Oakley...
- Who?
- Lele Pons...
- What?
- GloZell...
- Where?
- Joey Graceffa!
- When?
- Sunday. I already said that.
- Oh, I'm so embarrassed.
With special guest star,
everyone's favorite
Internet how-to whiz,
Corey from Corey's World.
What's going on, guys?
I'm Corey from Corey's World.
And I'm gonna be live and in-person
at the Quahog Streaming-Con,
where you'll see I'm only five-foot-two.
And remember, that Nazi stuff
I said was in the heat
of a very competitive Halo game.
And congratulations to Goldblatt69,
whose people definitely
do not control the media
and all banking.
Dad, can we go to Streaming-Con?
Well, I wasn't watching
all that closely.
Is it like a rodeo?
Um, sure.
We're going to Streaming-Con! Giddyup!
Looks like someone's
going to Streaming-Con.
Rope a doggy for me.
Oh, awesome. Look over there.
You can take a selfie
in a hospital bed
to get social media attention.
"Don't really want to get
into it, but I'm fine."
Oh, boy. Well, this is
the last thing I wanted.
I'm gonna do a Instagram story
here where I insult a loner
and it becomes a whole thing.
What's up, everybody?
I'm here at Streaming-Con 2019.
Weird ponytail.
They got a whole booth of cat GIFs here.
Jiff?
How-how do you say... Uh-oh.
Hey, man, I didn't say anything
to that guy.
This is ridiculous.
You're hurting my wrist!
So check this out, guys.
I got kicked out of Streaming-Con 2019.
Now, I don't know if anyone
watching this is a lawyer,
especially a constitutional lawyer,
but...
Hey.
Hey, guys, so I'm in my own trunk.
Uh, I think I'm gonna get murdered.
Uh, but before I do, I forgot,
I'm supposed to mention Triscuits.
Really, all the Nabisco products,
they're-they're solid.
You know, like, on the back of Triscuits
when they give you
the recipes for those snacks?
Like, the-the mini pizzas?
I swear to God,
make those little pizzas.
Hashtag it: #PetesTriscuitLifeHacks.
Go ahead and check it out.
Recipe in bio.
Whoa!
I got away.
Hey, guys, I'm in an Uber,
heading back to Streaming-Con.
Uh, man bun alert.
Now seating for
Corey: The Live Experience.
All religions welcome.
That's us! Come on, everyone!
Hey, where's Brian?
Hey, you know how Snapchat
puts a fake dog tongue on you?
How'd you like a real one?
- That was bad.
- Eh, times have changed.
Three years ago, I would've been a hero.
Three years ago, they would've been 12.
I need a nap.
Brian, turn on the heat and NPR.
We now return to NPR's Fresh Air.
My guest today is a white music writer
who has written a book
about the history of hip-hop.
Stewie's loss.
I'm sure this'll be
an enriching discussion.
Hip-hop has its roots in
the call-and-response tradition
of the Southern black Baptist church.
Well, a nap was
just what the doctor ordered.
- I feel like a new...
- And, of course, you can't
write a history of rap
without mentioning Gil Scott-Heron...
What's going on, guys?
I'm Corey from Corey's World.
And today, I'm gonna show you
how anyone can become
an Internet celebrity, like me,
Corey from Corey's World.
I bet you can't make my daughter
Meg an Internet celebrity.
Dad, stop.
No, stand up, young lady.
Rectangle body, fridge bod,
untapped market.
Go with that.
Everybody, hashtag #FridgeBodMeg.
You're welcome.
Oh, my God, Dad!
I'm trending on Twitter.
That's awesome, Meg.
I say we celebrate
by eating Triscuit pizzas.
- Is it good?
- The recipe's right on the box.
- Yeah, but is it good?
- You can make them
with ingredients you probably
already have in the house.
- Dad, what does it taste like?
- That's right.
Ugh! It's like I dropped
a tomato in some hay.
Yeah, it's like if a horse made a pizza.
Triscuits: make sure
you have a drink nearby.
All right, Meg, now that
you're an Internet personality,
we got to build your brand.
Is there anything you can do?
Uh, yeah, actually, I can...
I-Is...
Is there anything you can do
in front of your dad?
- I can shuffle a deck of cards.
- Oh, good.
With my...
All right, we're taking your
bedroom door off the hinges.
Is the lady who owns the Prius here?
- Uh, actually, that's me.
- Oh, well, your wife's car is totaled.
- It's my car.
- Sorry.
We were, however,
able to save your purse.
It's a gender-fluid Euro carrier.
Either way, we'll have it towed
back to San Francisco.
Hey, there are plenty of closer
gay cities, you big ape.
How did this turn into my fight?
You're gonna need a loaner.
We have a pink Volkswagen Beetle
you might feel comfortable in.
Ooh, Brian, we could be two in the pink!
Take that one! Take that one!
Yeah, I'm thinking
of something sportier.
- The red Miata it is.
- Give me your manliest car!
Bill, I need a Hummer.
Again? You're insatiable.
Wise guy.
Wow, that thing's big.
Brian, it's night now.
What's up? This is Refrigerator Meg.
Thought I'd give you a tour
of my refrigerator lifestyle.
Let's see what we've got in here.
Ooh, check, check, check it out!
Boom! Mini cream!
Oh, and what's this? Strawberry yogurt?
Is-is your girl Meg
some kind of health nut?
No, turn it around: 35 grams of sugar!
Yeah, through the roof!
Check it, check it, what's this?
A bacon drawer? Stacked.
Rashers on rashers.
Best part about these bad boys?
Don't even have to cook them.
Cook them right in your stomach!
Wash it down with a little cream!
Oh, boy, that's-that's going
right through me.
Sponsored by Oscar Mayer
and Land O'Lakes.
If it's not Land O'Lakes,
it's not cream!
Hey, Meg? You can't use the Charmin.
You're now sponsored by
Safeway Rough 'n' Thin.
Don't forget to wash the tip
of your middle finger
when you're done.
Mom, we've got a problem.
See, I-I promoted Magic Shell
ice cream topping on my channel,
- so-so they sent me a ton of it.
- Yeah, so?
Dad Han Solo'd himself.
Oh, my God, he's gonna suffocate.
I created a vanilla ice cream
Peter covered in Magic Shell.
- Why?
- Because I must.
Don't listen to him. He's an imposter.
- I'm the real Peter.
- No, you're not.
I made you. I'm the real Peter.
Oh-oh, my God, I-I don't know
which one to believe.
What do you mean?
I'm a guy, and he's ice cream.
Thank God, Lois.
Does anyone mind
if I turn the thermostat down
to 32 degrees?
There ain't a reason on Earth
to waste it
It ain't a crime to be good to yourself
Lick it up
Lick it up...
- Yeah?
- It's me.
Can you change the station?
Whoa, lick it up...
Don't need to wait...
Oh...
Oh, yeah...
Five different stations, all
playing "Lick It Up" by Kiss.
Hummer.
Well, it's nice of you
to once again drive me
to day care, Brian.
Sure. It's only three klicks away.
I just hope I don't
get branded a "Hummer guy."
I can feel the Earth warming.
No one needs a car this big.
Yes, but I like how
when you cut to an outside shot,
Sam Elliott is narrating your drive.
When you need
to take a talking baby to day care,
you'll move mountains.
And if the mountains won't move,
drive right over 'em.
Hummer.
And, yes, Big Lebowski fans,
I've seen the movie.
I don't need to hear the lines.
This place is paying Meg?
Uh, to do what?
Nothing. When you have
a million followers,
people just pay you to hang out.
Yo, yo, yo! Everything here
is made with corn syrup!
Just drink the corn syrup!
Oh, my God, she collapsed!
We got to get her to the hospital.
Don't want to wait
till you know me better...
Anybody need a ride to the hospital?
What?
Does anybody need a ride
to the hospital?
How is she?
- What?
- How is Meg?
I'm worried! Her pulse is very weak!
Her middle finger smells weird.
Meg has Type 2 diabetes.
The one where you're
supposed to shame her,
not feel sorry for her.
But I need to draw
a little more blood for the lab.
As I suspected. Sap.
- Vermont gold.
- I love sugaring season.
Me too.
"The moon, though slight,
was moon enough to show
"On every tree a bucket with a lid,
And on black ground,
a bearskin rug of snow."
Robert Frost,
"Evening In A Sugar Orchard."
Robert Frost!
What? Dad?
It's okay, Meg.
You had a diabetic coma dream.
Dad's still an idiot.
I'm still an idiot.
Coming up, local anchor brings
a concealed weapon to work,
as is his right.
But first, popular
Internet star Meg Griffin
has Type 2 diabetes,
and is also the new face
of diabetes drug Pancresta.
Refrigerator Meg here.
If diabetes has you down,
get your insulin levels up
with Pancresta.
Pancresta may cause heart disease,
swelling, allergic reactions.
Do not take Pancresta
if you are pregnant
or plan on becoming pregnant.
If you have a problem with addiction,
do not take Pancresta,
as smoking Pancresta may mimic
the otherworldly high of heroin.
Chopping up and snorting
Pancresta may amplify
and/or enhance sexual experience.
Rock concerts on Pancresta may
be excessively transformative.
Pancresta may cause
intense philosophical
and scientific breakthroughs.
Pancresta can be delivered
directly to your home,
and since we're here, why not,
we'll do a bump.
Pancresta is not for everyone,
just the sexy people.
Lame losers should not take Pancresta.
Pancresta.
Makes opiates look like
(BLEEP) baby aspirin.
Meg, like everyone
who doesn't have diabetes,
I'm not sure how it works,
but I do know you could go blind,
you could have organ failure,
you could lose your feet.
No amount of fame is worth this.
James Woods High School
will also be saluting
their own diabetic Internet celebrity
with a pep rally in her honor
this Thursday.
Sponsored by Pancresta,
which feels like being inside
the warm, wet mouth of the Lord.
You know, I think you like
driving this Hummer.
You're a Hummer guy.
I'm not a Hummer guy, Stewie.
I'm a responsible Prius driver
who's making the best
of a bad situation.
I didn't ask for this car.
I also didn't ask for these
slowpokes in front of me.
- Out of the way, you old bag!
- Brian, that's Paul McCartney
doing "Carpool Karaoke" songs
we can afford.
She'll be coming 'round
the mountain when she comes
Whoo!
How should we end the scene, Brian?
Sam Elliott or Kiss "Lick it Up"?
Why not both?
"Lick it up. Lick it up.
Oh, yeah."
That's about all I care to read of that.
Refrigerator Meg here
having one of my favorite snacks:
french fry sandwiches on white bread.
Bad sugars and starches are the bomb!
Meg's feet are gone. Rotted.
I have a gift for knowing
when something bad happens
to someone's legs,
kind of like a shining.
How you doing, doc?
Oh, you were thirsty, weren't you?
Good girl. No!
Good boy. You're a boy car.
- Yeah, that's weird. Stop that.
- Stop what?
The way you're touching, feeding,
- and talking to your car.
- His name is Mark McGrath.
What's happened to you?
I-I don't know. All I know
is I love this Hummer.
God, the power.
I deserved a sweet ride
for a little while.
It felt so good.
People turned their heads
when I pulled into Hooters,
Lids, GNC. It's not fair!
- How much creatine...
- I've been doing a lot of creatine!
All set.
You can probably get another
130,000 miles out of this thing.
Well, let's see...
I drive about 4,000 a year,
so when this car goes, I'll be...
Dead for 18 years.
Let me just say goodbye to the Hummer.
I'll miss you, Mark McGrath.
I'll miss scaring the hell
out of homeless people
with your cruise-ship-grade air horn.
I'll miss catching the eye of women
smoking outside of government buildings.
But mostly, I'll miss driving
a military vehicle
45 miles an hour through a school zone
to get Crest Whitestrips.
The back side of this car
is all wrecked.
Who fixed this thing, your wife?
- No, she can't fix a car.
- That's my point.
She passed away last month.
She was addicted to Pancresta,
so she didn't so much
pass away as elevate
to a higher level of consciousness.
Just turned into a smiling beam
of light right before my eyes.
She told me to be at peace, and I was.
I'm hearing a lot of good stuff
about this Pancresta.
Sorry, Mr. Griffin.
I don't know what happened.
Looks like you got the Hummer
for another couple of days at least.
Stewie, why did you do it?
Oh, you were having so much fun, Bri.
Besides, the Earth is on fire.
One dog driving a Prius won't fix that.
Where to?
Let's do donuts on Mark Ruffalo's lawn.
Yeah!
Hey, come on, you guys. Knock it off.
Hey, why don't you turn into the Hulk?
Oh, right. You're just
a Hollywood sissy.
I'm calling the cops!
Oh, you hear that, Brian?
Hulk's calling the cops.
Turns out old Mark really was the Hulk.
And Brian and Stewie got tossed
clear up to New Hampshire.
I'm Sam Elliott.
This concludes your B story.
Look at 'em all out there, Meg.
They're all here because of you.
Hi, Meg.
It's your friends,
Patty, Ruth and Esther.
If anyone remembered what we look like,
it would be shocking how fat we are.
You've inspired us
to gain all this weight,
and we just wanted to say thanks.
♪
Dad, I can't do this.
All my friends are fat because of me.
I don't want them
to lose their feet, too.
Everybody needs their feet.
Feet. Those little
weirdos on the end of your legs.
I used mine to mosey on over
to the A story.
I'm going out there to warn everybody
about the dangers of unhealthy eating.
Meg, I am so high
on Pancresta right now,
I don't care what you say.
Three dimensions?
No, six dimensions.
Be at peace, Meg.
Be at peace.
Phone. Forgot my phone.
- We love you, Meg!
- Eat something gross!
I was gonna take you to prom
as part of a cruel bet,
but I'm fat now, too!
Hey, everybody.
I want to talk to you guys
about something important.
Being healthy.
I'm still Refrigerator Meg!
But from here on, my fridge
will be full of fruits,
vegetables and lean meats! Yo, yo, yo!
Bring back the fridge!
Aah!
What's going on, guys?
I'm Corey from Corey's World.
Did you hear that all the Jewish kids
stayed home from school that day?
Is everyone okay, Principal Shepherd?
Mostly. We only had one fatality.
An old janitor was crushed
under the bleachers.
Huh. Has anyone claimed his feet?
Yeah, and has anyone claimed his mop?
Good news! The feet transplant
was a success.
So...
good news all around.
Well,
I'm glad everything's back to normal.
No, it isn't!
Meg got the dead janitor's feet,
Brian and Stewie got thrown
into New Hampshire by the Hulk,
and you're a beam of light.
I have the shining now.
And Chris has the shining now.
Lois, just do a line of Panc.
Ah! Road House!
Road House.
Road House...
is a movie I was in.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.tv